<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="title_dialog_change_name">Change Name</string>
    <string name="title_dialog_error">Error</string>
    <string name="title_dialog_info">Information</string>
    <string name="title_dialog_image_info">Image Information</string>
    <string name="title_dialog_confirmation">Confirmation</string>
    <string name="title_dialog_select_folder">Select Folder</string>
    <string name="title_dialog_tip">Tip</string>
    <string name="message_dialog_no_picture"><![CDATA[[HTML]There are no pictures in the input folder.<br><br>You may need to <a href="appcode://selectInputFolder">change the input folder</a> and restart this action.<br><br>Alternatively, you may now import photos from the gallery.]]></string>
    <string name="message_dialog_no_photos_for_name">No eye photos available</string>
    <string name="message_dialog_no_photos_in_input_folder">There are no pictures in the input folder. You may import photos from the gallery.</string>
    <string name="message_dialog_select_name">Please select a name</string>
    <string name="message_dialog_organized_photos">The selected photos have been organized. There are more photos that may be organized.</string>
    <string name="message_dialog_cannot_create_folder">Cannot create folder %1$s</string>
    <string name="message_dialog_cannot_write_to_folder">Cannot write to folder %1$s. Please select a different folder.</string>
    <string name="message_dialog_cannot_write_to_folder_saf">Cannot write to folder %1$s. Please ensure that you grant access rights for the full SD card.</string>
    <string name="message_dialog_cannot_change_date">The date of the photos of %1$s from %2$s cannot be changed to %3$s, as there are already photos for this date</string>
    <string name="message_dialog_no_organized_photos">There are no organized photos available for display. Please take first a pair of eye photos and assign name and date.</string>
    <string name="message_dialog_file_does_not_exist">File %1$s does not exist</string>
    <string name="message_dialog_failed_to_move_file">Failed to move file %1$s to %2$s</string>
    <string name="message_dialog_failed_to_move_folder_partially">Error while moving folder %1$s to %2$s - please check folders and move files to appropriate folder.</string>
    <string name="message_dialog_failed_to_rename_file">Failed to rename file %1$s to %2$s</string>
    <string name="message_dialog_failed_to_delete_file">Failed to delete the photo %1$s</string>
    <string name="message_dialog_failed_to_delete_all_files">Failed to delete all files of input folder</string>
    <string name="message_dialog_failed_to_delete_file_for_date">Failed to delete the photos of %1$s from %2$s</string>
    <string name="message_dialog_failed_to_move_file_for_date">Failed to move the photos of %1$s from %2$s</string>
    <string name="message_dialog_failed_to_delete_folder">Failed to delete the folder of %1$s</string>
    <string name="message_dialog_failed_to_change_date">Could not change date for photos of %1$s from %2$s to %3$s</string>
    <string name="message_dialog_failed_to_store_metadata">Failed to store metadata in file %1$s</string>
    <string name="message_dialog_failed_to_store_exif">Failed to store EXIF metadata in file %1$s - please contact the developer!</string>
    <string name="message_dialog_failed_to_access_camera">Failed to access the camera.\n\nError Details: %1$s</string>
    <string name="message_dialog_failed_to_use_camera2">Your device does not seem to support the Android 5 features of the camera. The app has now been reconfigured to use Android 4 compatibility. Please start the app again.</string>
    <string name="message_dialog_failed_to_open_google_play">Failed to open Google Play.</string>
    <string name="message_dialog_trial_names">In the trial version you are allowed to use only up to three names. Please purchase a premium pack to get unlimited access.</string>
    <string name="message_dialog_trial_time">The trial version of the app can be used only for two weeks. Please purchase a premium pack to get unlimited access.</string>
    <string name="message_dialog_trial_pending">Your purchase transaction of premium pack is pending. You can use the app as soon as the transaction is complete.</string>
    <string name="message_dialog_trial_overlays">The trial version of the app is limited to three overlays. Please purchase a premium pack to get unlimited access.</string>
    <string name="message_dialog_purchase_thanks">Thanks for your purchase!</string>
    <string name="message_dialog_purchase_thanks_premium">Thanks for your purchase! You can now use the app without limitations.</string>
    <string name="message_dialog_purchase_thanks_pending">Thanks for your purchase! As soon as the transaction is confirmed, you can use the app without limitations.</string>
    <string name="message_dialog_select_extsdcard">In the following Android dialog, please select the external SD card (either the full card or your selected folder) and confirm at the bottom.</string>
    <string name="message_dialog_select_photos_folder">In the following Android dialog, please select the folder where you want to store eye photos and confirm at the bottom.</string>
    <string name="message_dialog_select_input_folder">In the following Android dialog, please select the input folder for new eye photos and confirm at the bottom.</string>
    <string name="message_dialog_unformatted_file">File %1$s is not formatted correctly</string>
    <string name="message_dialog_confirm_delete_date">Do you really want to delete the photos of %1$s from %2$s?</string>
    <string name="message_dialog_confirm_delete_folder">Do you really want to delete %1$s with all photos?</string>
    <string name="message_dialog_confirm_delete_photo">Do you really want to delete the photo %1$s?</string>
    <string name="message_dialog_confirm_delete_two_photos">Do you really want to delete the two photos?</string>
    <string name="message_dialog_confirm_delete_all_photos">Do you really want to delete all photos from the input folder?</string>
    <string name="message_dialog_confirm_no_jpeg">The selected photos are no JPG photos. Therefore, part of the functionality (such as storing information) will not work. Do you want to continue?</string>
    <string name="message_dialog_confirm_overwrite">For the name “%1$s” there are already eye photos from %2$s. Do you want to overwrite these?\n\nOtherwise, please select a different name or date.</string>
    <string name="message_dialog_confirm_need_read_permission">This app needs to have permission on your external storage in order to access the images. Please provide this access - otherwise the app will not work.</string>
    <string name="message_dialog_confirm_need_camera_permission">Please provide access to the camera - otherwise the app will not work.</string>
    <string name="message_dialog_confirm_rate_app">If you like the app, then please recommend it.\n\nWould you like to rate it on Google Play?</string>
    <string name="message_dialog_confirm_rate_icon">Do you want to remove the rating icon from the app?</string>
    <string name="message_dialog_confirm_external_flash">Do you want to use an external LED flash connected to the headphone jack?</string>
    <string name="message_dialog_outofmemoryerror">The app has crashed due to lack of memory. If this happens repeatedly, then you should go to the settings, change the setting “Show image in full resolution” to the value “Load only on demand”, and reduce the value of “Max Bitmap size”.</string>
    <string name="message_dialog_hints_will_be_shown">From now on, the app will show hints in various situations (including the ones that you switched off earlier). You can switch them off individually.</string>
    <string name="message_dialog_no_hints_will_be_shown">From now on, the app will not show any of the currently existing hints. New hints of future versions will be shown.</string>
    <string name="message_dialog_triggering_purchase">Triggering purchase on Google Play&#8230;</string>
    <string name="message_guide_resize_iris">Please resize the eye until the iris fills the circle. Then press “OK”.</string>
    <string name="message_guide_resize_pupil">Please resize the eye until the pupil fills the circle. Then press “OK”.</string>
    <string name="imageinfo_line_filename">File name:</string>
    <string name="imageinfo_line_filedate">File date:</string>
    <string name="imageinfo_line_name">Name:</string>
    <string name="imageinfo_line_comment">Comment:</string>

</resources>