<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="releasenotes_title">Release Notes</string>
    <string name="releasenotes_changes">Latest Changes</string>
    <string name="releasenotes_release">Release</string>
    <string name="releasenotes_first_usage">
<![CDATA[
<h3>Information for new users:</h3>

<p>The purpose of this app is the organization and display of eye photos. On first usage, you need
to do the following:</p>
<p>1. Define an incoming folder for new eye photos and copy all your existing eye photos into this folder</p>
<p>2. Configure this folder as &ldquo;Input folder&rdquo; in the settings (first entry).</p>
<p>3. Assign these photos to persons and dates and shift them to the app&apos;s eye photo folder, using the &ldquo;Organize new photos&rdquo; functionality.</p>
<p>After this preparation, you can use the &ldquo;Display photos&rdquo; functionality to view and analyze your photos.</p>

<p>On most pages of the app you find a question mark on the top right corner - here you can access the help page.</p>

<p>There is an accompanying Windows application that can be used to view the photos that have been
organized with this app. For more information, see
<a href="http://augendiagnose.jeisfeld.de/?page=windowsapp">http://augendiagnose.jeisfeld.de/?page=windowsapp</a>.</p>

<p><b>Important remark:</b> This app modifies your JPG files in a non-destructive way, in order to store metadata within
the files. This has the advantage that all such information is still available if you
copy the pictures from one device to another one. To some extent, information like comments
will be even available when viewing the files in MS Windows. However, this kind of storage imposes a small risk.
It may happen that on some devices, or for pictures from some cameras, storing information in the JPG fails, or possibly
even destroys the JPG file. Therefore, it is recommended that you keep backups of your JPG files
when using the app for the first time with a new device or with a new camera. Please inform me if such problems appear.</p>
]]>
    </string>
    <string name="releasenotes_current_remark"></string>

    <string-array name="releasenotes_version_names" translatable="false">
        <item>0.1</item>
        <item>0.2</item>
        <item>0.2.1</item>
        <item>0.2.2</item>
        <item>0.2.3</item>
        <item>0.2.4</item>
        <item>0.2.5</item>
        <item>0.2.6</item>
        <item>0.2.7</item>
        <item>0.2.8</item>
        <item>0.2.9</item>
        <item>0.2.10</item>
        <item>0.3</item>
        <item>0.3.1</item>
        <item>0.3.2</item>
        <item>0.3.3</item>
        <item>0.4</item>
        <item>0.4.1</item>
        <item>0.4.2</item>
        <item>0.4.3</item>
        <item>0.4.4</item>
        <item>0.4.5</item>
        <item>0.4.6</item>
        <item>0.4.7</item>
        <item>0.4.8</item>
        <item>0.4.9</item>
        <item>0.4.10</item>
        <item>0.4.11</item>
        <item>0.4.12</item>
        <item>0.4.13</item>
        <item>0.5</item>
        <item>0.5.1</item>
        <item>0.5.2</item>
        <item>0.5.3</item>
        <item>0.5.4</item>
        <item>0.5.5</item>
        <item>0.5.6</item>
        <item>0.5.7</item>
        <item>0.5.8</item>
        <item>0.5.9</item>
        <item>0.5.10</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="releasenotes_version_notes">
        <item>Initial version. Allows to organize photos into a target folder, and to display pairs of photos.</item>
        <item>Added basic overlay functionality.</item>
        <item>Minor fixes.</item>
        <item>Added custom overlay.</item>
        <item>Added selection of alternative photos when organizing.</item>
        <item>Improved mapping of brightness/contrast.</item>
        <item>Various minor improvements and fixes.</item>
        <item>Added English version of overlay.</item>
        <item>Enabled starting the App from outside with a set of images</item>
        <item>Enable non-JPG images. Consider EXIF orientation of image.</item>
        <item>Added a second custom overlay. Improved overlay pinching. Corrected some display issues.</item>
        <item>Added various help screens.</item>
        <item>Enabled storage of Overlay position within JPG file.</item>
        <item>Added one more (Italian) overlay. Added start screen for new users. Bugfixes.</item>
        <item>Added context menu in image view. Allowed storage of contrast and brightness. Allowed editing of image comments. Minor improvements.</item>
        <item>Enabled to delete photos and change dates via context menu. Minor improvements and bugfixes.</item>
        <item>Introduced special design for tablets - merged list of names with list of photos per name</item>
        <item>Allowed storage of image position and zoom. Enablement of overlays and scrollbars in two-image view.</item>
        <item>While editing the comment, the image is still shown. Bugfixes.</item>
        <item>It is now possible to search for names. When organizing photos, new names can be entered more directly.</item>
        <item>Bugfixes</item>
        <item>Simplified folder selection in settings.</item>
        <item>Enabled moving photos back to the input folder. The app stays with organizing photos if there are more photos to be organized.</item>
        <item>Added navigation on help pages. Bugfixes.</item>
        <item>New overlays. Choose color of overlays. Bugfixes.</item>
        <item>Added one more overlay. Help page for release notes. Bugfixes.</item>
        <item>Changed scale on contrast bar. Enabled saving on ext sd card for Android 4.4. Spanish localization.</item>
        <item>Added one more overlay.</item>
        <item>Bugfixes - among others, fixed issues with upper case file extensions ("JPG")</item>
        <item>Enable language change. Enable sorting by last name. Enabled deletion of photos from input folder. Display latest eye photo pairs on top. Bugfixes</item>
        <item>When displaying images, instead of using a context menu, there is now an action bar. Display of the current picture detail in full resolution. Bugfixes.</item>
        <item>Display automatically in full resolution. Note: If this update leads to crashes or to bad performance of the app on your device, you should change the setting &amp;ldquo;Show image in full resolution&amp;rdquo;</item>
        <item>Changed options for display in full resolution due to issues with low memory devices</item>
        <item>Bugfixes</item>
        <item>Enabled saving on ext sd card for Android 5. Bugfixes</item>
        <item>Bugfixes</item>
        <item>Added dialogs with tips. Improved error handling.</item>
        <item>Allow to display image info while looking at image. Released Windows application. Bugfixes</item>
        <item>Take pictures directly from the app. Allow use of different SD cards for Input and Photos. Bugfixes</item>
        <item>Bugfixes</item>
        <item>Bugfixes</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>