<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="releasenotes_title">Release Notes</string>
    <string name="releasenotes_changes">Latest Changes</string>
    <string name="releasenotes_release">Release</string>
    <string name="button_dont_show">Do not show again</string>
    <string name="button_show_later">Show again</string>
    <string name="releasenotes_current_remark">
<![CDATA[
<h3>Important Note:</h3><p>The app stores information (like iris position or comments) directly
in the JPG image files. This has the advantage that all such information is still available if you
copy the pictures from one device to another one. To some extent, information like comments
will be even available when viewing the files in MS Windows.</p>

<p>However, this kind of storage imposes a small risk. It may happen that on some devices, or for 
pictures from some cameras, it may happen that storing information in the JPG fails, or possibly
even destroys the JPG file. Therefore, it is recommended that you keep backups of your JPG files
when using the app for the first time with a new device or with a new camera.</p>

<p>Please inform me if such problems appear.</p>
]]>
    </string>

    <string-array name="releasenotes_version_names" translatable="false">
        <item>0.1</item>
        <item>0.2</item>
        <item>0.2.1</item>
        <item>0.2.2</item>
        <item>0.2.3</item>
        <item>0.2.4</item>
        <item>0.2.5</item>
        <item>0.2.6</item>
        <item>0.2.7</item>
        <item>0.2.8</item>
        <item>0.2.9</item>
        <item>0.2.10</item>
        <item>0.3</item>
        <item>0.3.1</item>
        </string-array>
    <string-array name="releasenotes_version_notes">
        <item>Initial version. Allows to organize photos into a target folder, and to display pairs of photos.</item>
        <item>Added basic overlay functionality.</item>
        <item>Minor fixes.</item>
        <item>Added custom overlay.</item>
        <item>Added selection of alternative photos when organizing.</item>
        <item>Improved mapping of brightness/contrast.</item>
        <item>Various minor improvements and fixes.</item>
        <item>Added English version of overlay.</item>
        <item>Enabled starting the App from outside with a set of images</item>
        <item>Enable non-JPG images. Consider EXIF orientation of image.</item>
        <item>Added a second custom overlay. Improved overlay pinching. Corrected some display issues.</item>
        <item>Added various help screens.</item>
        <item>Enabled storage of Overlay position within JPG file.</item>
        <item>Added one more (Italian) overlay. Bugfixes.</item>
        </string-array>

</resources>